Title: Iron Ball EP03
story: TGPGTGX007054
lang: GBR
SOM: 10:00:00:00
It's a fierce battle to become
the national dodgeball team.
Iron Ball, Dodgeball Battle.
Us?
Is that even possible?
Ready.
"The Strongest Player Contest"
"The two teams that were chosen"
"Through fiery matches"
"Team Red is led by Kim Seung-min"
-Salute.
-Iron.
"Versus Team Blue led
by Jeong Hae-chul"
It's the Ten-person Elimination
that will produce
the first elimination.
"Ten-person Elimination"
Ten?
The losing team in round one
will eliminate three players.
The three players
from the losing team
will be selected after a discussion
between the managers and coaches.
All right,
we will now begin the first round.
Jump. Good.
-Come in.
-Nice.
"A dodgeball battle
with their survival on the line"
Okay.
"However"
"Due to lack of passing skills
and organizational skills"
Team Red lost in the first round
of the Ten-person Elimination"
The players eliminated
in the first round is
Jang Tae-pung, Jeong Seong-hoon,
and Jeong Jong-hyun.
"Players eliminated
in the first round"
"of the Ten-person Elimination"
"Jang Tae-pung,
Jeong Seong-hun, Jeong Jong-hyun"
"It's raining cats and dogs"
We will now begin round two
of the elimination.
The second round
will be a ten-on-ten match.
Since the players from Team Red
have been eliminated,
the number of members
has been reduced to ten.
As we will have a ten-on-ten match
to even out the number
of members from Team Blue
who won the first round,
three outstanding players
will sit out from the match.
Outstanding players?
It means we'll play fair.
I never expected that.
I will announce it now.
The first person
of the top three players is...
The first player is
"The first player is"
Oh Jong-hyuk.
-Okay.
-Nice.
"Accuracy"
"Agility"
Look at the ball.
"A certified ace, Oh Jong-hyuk"
The second outstanding player
is Kim Geon.
-Kim Geon did well.
-Kim Geon.
"An active inside attacker,
Kim Geon"
Good.
"He has high-level explosiveness
and ball control"
He's outstanding as an attacker.
The third outstanding player is
"Who is the last
outstanding player?"
Song Bo-geun.
Song Bo-geun!
It's Song Bo-geun.
"There's no ball I can't avoid"
"Crazy reflexes"
-Bo-geun is good at dodging.
-Yes.
"Song Bo-geun, the agile body"
You've been chosen based
on your competitiveness.
The three of you
will not compete in round two.
Except for these three,
the ten players from Team Blue
and the ten remaining members
of Team Red
will compete against each other.
Players will be eliminated
in this round.
How will the match be played?
There will be
no winning or losing teams.
Three players will be eliminated.
"Individual skill
is an absolute factor in scoring"
Players from both teams
will be eliminated.
Then there's no point in winning.
The player eliminated
will depend on the match.
You can show your skills
however you want.
You just have to do your best.
"The players are in deep thought"
"Because of round two's elimination"
Since it's all up
to the head coach and coach,
we can only do our best.
They haven't seen my true worth yet.
So I'm gritting my teeth a bit.
The second round will determine
the three eliminated players.
Okay, both teams,
please take your positions.
"Prepare to attack"
-Come on!
Like I said, be confident.
Pass freely,
but be ready to coordinate.
That's how you can stop
Chung-won's passes.
We're at the beach.
Block it like a catcher.
Like this. A catcher's pose.
Winning or losing isn't important.
I think the quality
of the match is more important.
We just need to play well.
-Go! Fight!
-Woo!
Is Seung-min serving again?
Yes, Seung-min should go.
Don't force yourself.
Play just like earlier.
-Team Blue.
-Woo!
Go!
Show some spirit!
Dodgeball is all about spirit.
Both teams, please switch positions.
"Before the match,
both teams switch positions"
We can do it.
We played a lot of games.
It doesn't matter if we win or lose.
Just do our best.
We just have to do our best.
"Team Blue's high-speed outfielder,
Kim Seung-min"
No matter who wins,
three players will be eliminated.
Focus.
Stay calm.
We have to play well.
"Arena of clouds"
Okay, the game is about to start.
"Kim Sang-wook from Team Red"
"Lee Dong-gyu from Team Blue"
"Which team will attack first?"
"The ball is thrown"
-It's okay.
-Defend!
"Team Blue attacks quickly
as soon as they get the jump ball"
"Lee Ju-yong's powerful shot"
Defend.
That's it.
Ju-yong is doing well now.
"Lee Ju-yong is showing off
his offensive power from the start"
Offensive formation.
Hwang Chung-won
is now an outfielder.
"Park Do-hyeon passes"
"Team Red advances
with a low and fast pass"
Nice.
"He dodges it low"
"Lee Ju-yong ducks even lower"
"Lee Ju-yong, good boy"
"Rapid play tactic"
Nice.
"He missed"
Nice!
It's okay.
Chung-won often
makes mistakes like that.
Chung-won!
Block the ball from below
with your body.
"Sorry"
It's okay. Defence formation!
-Defence formation!
-Defence.
"Lee Dong-gyu attacks"
"The ball goes out of bounds"
Nice...
You have to be careful
when you attack here.
In the infield.
We can't do that. That won't work.
"Team Red attacks"
It's Hwang Chung-won again.
"Intercepts a long-range pass
from Team Red"
Nice catch by Gu Seong-hwi.
"Team Blue begins to counterattack"
"Lee Jin-bong tries to intercept"
Lee Jin-bong is very powerful.
Because he even tries
to catch a ball from the outside.
Others just avoid it.
"Team Blue's infield attack
fails again"
"Lee Min-gon's powerful shot"
"Goes out of bounds"
"Team Blue can't connect
to the offence"
-Stay calm.
-Stay calm. You're doing well.
Very good.
Let's eliminate one of them first.
Let's focus on eliminating
one of them first.
We can try.
-Catch the ball.
-Okay.
Hwang Chung-won's ball
is really fast.
"Team Red's stable passing tactic"
Catch the ball.
Come on, Lee Jin-bong.
"Bong-ki's fire shot"
"Hit!
"Replay"
"Kim Min-jun from Team Blue is out"
Kim Min-jun is out.
"Shakes his head"
"Team Red Hwang Chung-won's
strong attack continues"
"General Hwang's powerful shot"
Catch it!
"A powerful shot that even
his teammates can't handle"
Slowly.
"Hwang Chung-won, Choi Seong-hyeon"
-Nice.
-It rolled over.
"Miss"
Very good.
Take your time.
What a shame.
He should have caught it.
"Lee Dong-gyu's impatient attack"
"causes Team Blue to lose
the right to attack"
I'm sorry. I was too impatient.
Dong-gyu, don't get too worked up.
Look at him.
"Team Red is on the attack again"
"Bong-ki's tornado shoot"
"Successful attack"
HID's Lee Min-gon is out.
"Team Blue attacks"
Blue.
Nice.
Be ready to receive
the ball at all times.
"Team Blue misses the ball"
"Bong-ki seizes the chance"
He caught it.
"Gu Seong-hwi catches the ball
and follows up with an attack"
-Nice.
-Nice, Gu Seong-hwi.
"Get hit, Bong-ki"
Be ready to receive
the ball at all times.
Yes!
Nice, Gu Seong-hwi.
Lee Jin-bong is out.
Lee Jin-bong
is overly aggressive again.
-In a situation like that...
-He should have dodged it quickly.
He didn't have
to catch it every time.
Line.
"Team Blue 7, Team Red 8"
Again.
Come out.
"Is it out of bounds?"
"Kim Jeong-woo saves the ball
with his quick movement"
Chung-won, get the ball.
"He shoots it softly"
"Lee Ju-yong from Team Blue is out"
"Kim Jeong-woo, who can play
both offence and defence"
"Team Red, who's on a roll,
is on the attack"
"Gu Seong-hwi from Team Blue is out"
That's too bad.
I should've caught that one.
"Team Blue 5, Team Red 8"
"Team Blue attacks"
Here.
"Team Blue's counterattack"
"Lee Dong-gyu, Lee Min-gon"
"They must hit someone this time!"
"Park Do-hyeon dodges
with an explosive force"
Nice.
"Kim Min-jun misses the ball
because of his slow reflexes"
"Team Red has
an overwhelming attack rate"
Take a breath. Let's go.
Fight!
Focus.
"Team Red's outfield pass"
Watch the line.
It's okay.
One more time...
Are you okay?
Let's finish it
in the outfield this time.
Let's finish it in one go.
"Intercepts the pass"
"Someone who knows
the attack pattern"
"Park Jun-woo intercepts"
"Then attacks"
Nice.
"Park Jun-woo and Kim Seung-min
succeed in combining tactics"
Nice.
Park Jun-woo did a good job.
That was a good point.
Intercept, pass, and attack.
Get ready.
Be ready to react right away.
"Team Blue 5, Team Red 7"
Throw it. Just throw it.
"Nervous"
"Team Blue attacks"
"Kim Jeong-woo jumps"
Good job.
"Kim Jeong-woo
shows off his agility"
Ours.
Here we go.
Finish it. Finish at once.
Block it. That's it.
Good.
Out.
Get the ball.
Nice.
"A feint attack without looking"
Nice!
Good!
Get the ball.
"Park Gil-yeon attacks
while pretending to pass"
"Kim Jeong-woo is out"
"Team Blue 5, Team Red 6"
"Over here"
"Confirmed eye contact"
"Kim Jeong-woo, Choi Seong-hyeon"
Nice.
-Nice...
-Good.
"Kim Jeong-woo, Choi Seong-hyeon's
fantastic teamwork"
Nice, Jeong-woo.
"Lee Dong-gyu from Team Blue is out"
Let's go.
"Team Blue 4, Team Red 6"
Pass the ball.
"Oh Sang-young shoots"
Good.
"Jeong Hae-chul
from Team Red is out"
Good.
"Team Blue 4, Team Red 5"
"Team Blue is chasing Team Red"
Here.
"Outfield long-range pass"
Nice. Attack.
"Attacks right away"
"Kang Jun from Team Red is out"
"Team Blue eliminates two in a row"
"Team Red's turn to attack again"
"Lee Yu Jeong from Team Blue is out"
It's a hit!
"Team Blue continues to fight back"
"Kim Sang-wook from Team Red is out"
"Team Blue 3, Team Red 3"
Okay, it's three to three.
"Team Blue's last three"
"Park Gil-yeon"
"Oh Sang-young"
"Park Jun-woo"
"Team Red's last three"
"Kang Cheong-myung"
"Choi Seong-hyeon, Park Do-hyeon"
The remaining ones
are pretty strong.
It's not easy.
"It's neck and neck,
it's anyone's game"
"Team Blue attacks"
Get ready to receive.
"Park Do-hyeon slips"
"It's a chance!"
Let's continue right away.
"Park Do-hyeon dodges"
"Oh Sang-young spikes"
Nice.
"Park Do-hyeon dodges again"
"Too bad"
"Exclaiming"
-Park Do-hyeon.
-He's quick.
Park Do-hyeon is agile.
That's because he trained his core.
"Replay"
"Park Do-hyeon,
the master of dodging"
They often hit it to the back.
-Seong-hyeon, hit it to the back.
-Okay.
-Take your time.
-Let's go.
Let's go.
Okay, straight pass.
Okay.
"Oh Sang-young intercepts"
Nice.
Oh Sang-young.
"Team Blue's turn to attack again"
Nice.
-Park Do-hyeon, nice catch.
-Park Do-hyeon!
He's showing his skills.
Park Do-hyeon, nice catch.
Be ready at all times.
Cheong-myung.
"After passing to the outfielder"
"Successful attack"
"Catches"
"A powerful shot"
Chung-won is doing well.
Hwang Chung-won is too strong.
He's the real deal.
Oh Sang-young is out.
Fight! Go! We did well!
-Good.
-We're doing well.
Seong-hyeon, good job!
Catch the ball.
Get ready to catch the ball.
-It's a hit.
-Good.
"Kang Cheong-myung
from Team Red is out"
He could have caught that ball.
He should have tried
to catch it instead of dodging it.
"Team Blue 2, Team Red 2"
"Hwang Chung-won's attack"
Park Gil-yeon is out.
Okay, it's two to one now.
Gather around.
It's okay.
Ready...
"Super nervous"
It's a three-point chance.
"Park Jun-woo defends,
Team Red attacks"
"Park Jun-woo takes control
of the attack"
"Shoots right away"
It's a hit!
"Park Do-hyeon from Team Red is out"
Nice.
We're doing very well so far.
You don't know
when the ball will come at you.
So be ready at all times.
Okay?
Okay.
How will the match end?
"Park Jun-woo versus
Choi Seong-hyeon"
"Who will be
the last player standing?"
"Team Blue attacks"
"No wonder he's
the last player remaining"
"Lee Ju-yong missed
the golden opportunity"
He misses it because he
can't grasp the speed of the ball.
Get ready.
Be ready for the ball at all times.
-It's the last one.
-Go!
"He tries to use this attack
to attack Team Red"
"Team Red attacks"
-Attack!
-You must hit him.
"Kang Jun's attack"
"Must avoid it at all costs"
Attack!
"Kang Jun, Park Jun-woo"
"What will happen?"
"Will Park Jun-woo catch
the ball successfully?"
Attack!
"Park Jun-woo from Team Blue is out"
"Park Jun-woo
couldn't catch the ball"
"Choi Seong-hyeon,
the last man standing"
Very good.
Good job...
You played very calmly. Well done.
Your defence was good too.
You played much better
than in the first round.
You're stable.
"Team Red successfully avenges
the first round"
"Meanwhile, Team Blue"
-I'm sorry.
-It's okay.
I should've caught it better.
"Team Blue is sad to lose"
"The coaches are selecting
the eliminated players"
After watching the second round,
we can see how to evaluate those
-who are not eliminated.
-Yes.
Is he bad if he is out early?
It's also easier for those
in front to be eliminated.
If you hold out by hiding,
I don't think it's meaningful.
The other thing is
when the ball is thrown at you,
there are people who prepare for it.
The ball can be used
to your advantage or disadvantage.
Occasionally, players will miss
because they're not ready.
That's one
of the criteria for judging.
We can see that.
"The coaches are serious
about their final discussion"
This guy.
The second one...
Actually, it's these two.
He's more aggressive
than this player.
"Which three will be eliminated
after the coaches' evaluation?"
"The weather continues to worsen"
The results for round two of
the Ten-person Elimination are in.
Team Red won
by surviving to the end.
It was announced earlier
that winning didn't matter
in the second round.
We will now announce
the three eliminated players
from both teams.
Compared to round one,
there has been
a noticeable improvement
in your strategic moves
in offence and defence.
It's great that you're executing
your strategies boldly.
I will now announce
the three eliminated players
from round two
out of the 20 players.
"Who will be eliminated?"
Who will be eliminated?
We will now announce
the first eliminated player.
The first eliminated player is
Kim Min-jun.
It's Kim Min-jun.
"Kim Min-jun from Team Blue"
Kim Min-jun from Team Blue
is the first to be eliminated.
"Kim Min-jun is the first
to be eliminated"
Kim Min-jun is out.
"Shakes his head"
"He's defenceless
even in the outfield"
"Kim Min-jun often makes mistakes
during the match"
As expected, a player from
the losing team has been called out.
Kim Min-jun has been eliminated.
Who will be
the second eliminated player
between the two teams?
"Announcing the second elimination
of round two"
The second eliminated player is
"The second eliminated player is"
"Nervous"
Kang Cheong-myung.
"Kang Cheong-myung from Team Red"
"Out while dodging"
He should try
to catch it instead of dodging it.
The final eliminated player
for round two
following Kang Cheong-myung.
Will he be from Team Red
or Team Blue?
Please reveal the result.
The third eliminated player is...
"What will happen?"
Lee Yu-jeong.
Lee Yu-jeong
from Team Blue.
"He wasn't in his best condition
during the match"
-Be safe.
-Catch it.
He didn't catch the ball,
so he has no presence.
He's too cautious.
The three players
have been eliminated.
It was my first time
playing dodgeball.
It was harder than I thought.
It's a very difficult sport.
I'm glad I got to play it
with you all.
I hope the remaining members
will do well.
-Thank you.
-Good job.
It's a shame, but since
I received such an evaluation,
I'll accept it and go home
with no regrets.
Okay.
I haven't played
a lot of sports with balls.
I think this was a good opportunity
for me to learn about balls.
The three of you did a good job.
Let's give them a round of applause
and say goodbye.
"Says goodbye
to their sweaty teammates"
-Gosh.
-No, don't be sad.
-Don't be sad.
-You did a good job.
Don't get hurt. Be careful.
Don't get hurt.
Please make it to the national team.
You did well.
I really did my best.
-It's my capability.
-You practised for so long.
You're really ready now
that you've trained.
Yes, really.
You did well.
The three of you did a good job.
But honestly, we did our best.
We weren't good enough.
Anyway, that's how it is.
Regardless of what we wanted to do,
our goal was
to be on the national team.
We can't be vague.
We have to do well.
You have to be good to be chosen
since you have
to wear the Korean flag
and play against other countries.
So you have to do well.
You did a good job.
Wasn't it fun?
"The three eliminated players
put their regrets behind them"
Since three people were eliminated
in rounds one and two,
a total of six members
were eliminated.
There are now 20 players left.
"Nine people on Team Red survive,
eleven people on Team Blue survive"
Now, we will eliminate
four more players.
So in the third round,
it will be a match
to eliminate four players.
Now, the head coach and the coach
will announce the ten survivors.
The ten players who are called out
will be designated
as today's survivors.
"Today's designated survivors"
This is crazy.
We'll announce the ten survivors.
The three remaining players
from round one
will automatically advance.
So, Oh Jong-hyuk,
Song Bo-geun, and Kim Geon.
These three automatically advance.
We need to announce
the remaining seven survivors.
"There are seven spots left"
We will announce
the remaining seven survivors
apart from the three.
The fourth player to survive is
Park Jun-woo.
Park Jun-woo survives.
Next, the fifth survivor is
Choi Seong-hyeon.
Choi Seong-hyeon!
Kim Seung-min.
The captain, Kim Seung-min.
Park Do-hyeon...
There are three players left.
Now, the eighth survivor is
"If they don't make it,
they're in danger of elimination"
Gu Seong-hwi...
Gu Seong-hwi survives.
Next is the ninth survivor.
"The ninth player to survive"
Jeong Hae-chul...
Jeong Hae-chul.
The captain survives.
There's only one spot left.
The last one.
The last player to survive.
"The last player to survive"
The last survivor is
Kim Jeong-woo.
Kim Jeong-woo survives.
"Both joy and sorrow after
the ten survivors are selected"
So the ten players
who didn't get called out
and the ten players who survived...
A match?
You will have the final match.
It's to show off our performance.
It's the last chance.
The ten of you
are not on the survivor list.
After the final match,
six of you will be saved
and four of you will be eliminated.
This is so cruel. My goodness.
The ten players who survived...
and ten players
who didn't survive...
will have the final match.
Four of you
will be eliminated in the end.
"Team Survivor"
"Oh Jong-hyuk,
Kim Geon, Song Bo-geun"
"Park Jun-woo, Choi Seong-hyeon"
"Kim Seung-min,
Park Do-hyeon, Gu Seong-hwi"
"Jeong Hae-chul, Kim Jeong-woo"
"Team Crisis"
"Lee Jin-bong,
Lee Dong-gyu, Hwang Chung-won"
"Park Gil-yeon, Lee Min-gon"
"Kim Sang-wook,
Kang Jun, Yoon Jong-jin"
"Oh Sang-young, Lee Ju-yong"
The third round
will be between the ten players
who are guaranteed to survive
and the ten players whose survival
haven't been decided yet.
From now on,
the third round begins.
"The third round begins"
Do we have to continue
even if it's raining?
We have to continue.
Let's take a break and regroup.
"Confused"
Okay, let's take a break
and regroup.
There's lightning.
"There's lightning
and the rain is getting heavier"
There's lightning.
"The staff takes shelter
from the heavy rain"
What should we do?
Let's get out of the rain.
One, two, three!
"Filming is interrupted"
Take a break.
Why is it raining so much?
"The heavy rain prevents
the match from proceeding"
This is crazy.
Are we not going to compete?
We're going
to keep going today, right?
It doesn't look like
we can continue.
-Right?
-Yes.
So...
Okay, focus.
Okay, the microphone.
Yes.
"The players regroup"
Due to the sudden downpour,
the staff had a meeting.
In the spirit of the Iron Ball,
we will proceed
with the third round.
What do you think? Is that okay?
Yes...
-Is that okay?
-Yes!
Okay, let's move on
to the third round.
Round three.
We'll start
with no outfield players.
"For careful evaluation,
all players will be in the infield"
No outfield players on either side.
I hope those of you
who have survived
will also do your best
for the other team.
Round three begins now.
You can do it!
Go for it!
"Only six people
from Team Crisis can survive"
-Come on, fight!
-Woo!
-Go! Strong!
Do your best!
Let's fight for real!
Elimination or no elimination,
I want to break the label.
We have to survive
because this is the last one.
This time, it's really do or die.
"Jump ball to determine who starts"
Okay, let's focus.
Come on, focus on the ball.
"Gu Seong-hwi from Team Survivors"
"Lee Dong-gyu from Team Crisis"
We have to win no matter what.
"Team Crisis attacks first"
-Let's go!
-Go!
Nice catch!
Okay!
"The ball is slippery
because of the rain"
The ball is very slippery.
"Lee Dong-gyu
from Team Crisis attacks"
Okay!
It's slippery.
"Oh Jong-hyuk
from Team Survivors attacks"
"Slippery"
The ball is slippery now.
-Because of the rain.
-Yes, it's slippery.
-It's really slippery.
-I know.
The ball is slippery.
Avoid it if you can.
Okay.
Don't receive the ball.
You'll be at a disadvantage.
-It's raining too hard.
-Hurry.
Avoid it if you can.
The ball will go over.
Go, Geon!
"Kim Geon
from Team Survivor attacks"
"A high-speed ball"
"Lee Dong-gyu is out"
-Okay.
-Lee Dong-gyu moves to the outfield.
We have an outfield player now.
We now have an outfield player.
-We have an outfield player.
-An outfield player at the back.
"Team Survivor is in a crisis"
"The ball bounces high because
Kim Jeong-woo can't catch it"
-Catch it.
-Come on.
You have to catch it.
"Song Bo-geun flies immediately"
Catch it.
"He fails to catch it"
Nice.
"Replay"
You have to catch it.
-Nice.
-Two people are out.
"Kim Jeong-woo
and Song Bo-geun are out"
Two people are out.
Okay, two people out.
-Go to the back.
-Okay.
"At that moment,
Lee Jin-bong suddenly sneaks up"
Jin-bong is moving forward
confidently.
Doesn't that mean he'll take it?
"Lee Jin-bong gets hits and is out?"
Okay.
Did he get out on purpose?
Lee Jin-bong.
-I think he got out on purpose.
-Jin-bong got out on purpose.
We need to make good use
of the outfield.
I think the team
that goes outfield early will win.
That means he's going to attack
from the outside.
Yes, he's going to play
He prepared a lot.
Side!
"Oh Sang-young's outfield side pass"
Okay, out.
Out.
-It's slippery.
-Okay.
"Park Jun-woo fails to block
the slippery ball and is out"
Nice.
"Nice!"
I'll go out.
Good.
"Yoon Jong-jin's
sharp outfield pass"
-Lee Dong-gyu is good. Nice.
-Rush attack!
Not bad, Dong-gyu. Not bad at all.
Gil-yeon, go!
Go!
"Lee Dong-gyu signals
to aim at Kim Geon"
Go!
"Park Gil-yeon, Lee Dong-gyu"
He got hit.
What? Are you going to pass it over?
"Fixes sight
and shoots without looking"
He got hit.
What? Are you going to pass it over?
He got hit. Yes, it's a hit.
Good job.
"Lee Dong-gyu
and Park Gil-yeon's linked play"
"Lee Ju-yong
from Team Crisis attacks"
Go!
"Connecting Lee Dong-gyu's ball
in the outfield"
Nice!
-Nice!
-Out!
"Lee Dong-gyu's fastball"
It's a hit.
"Choi Seong-hyeon
from Team Survivor is out"
We can win.
Once they're on the outfield,
the tactics are clear.
We'll move around, so don't worry.
Slowly.
-That's good.
-Good.
Okay, focus.
We can really win.
Finish them off!
Now that they have a clear goal,
it makes a difference.
-That's right.
-It's a desperate difference.
Go!
"Lee Jin-bong"
Take your time.
Focus.
My body is getting warm.
Okay.
-Nice.
-Good.
"Lee Jin-bong connects"
"But it's an empty attack"
He keeps making unnecessary attacks.
"Team Crisis' rhythm is interrupted"
-Ready.
-Pass the ball.
"Team Survivor fights back"
It's okay.
Nice.
Catch it.
Kang Jun.
It's okay.
Kang Jun's skills are also mediocre.
Ready.
"One pass"
That's right.
Again. Infield.
Infield. You can just hit it.
Nice, Sang-wook.
"Three passes in a row"
You have to attack.
Come on, gather around.
"Lee Jin-bong's four pass foul"
You have to make a move.
Come on, gather around.
Four pass foul.
Shoot.
Right away.
"Lee Jin-bong keeps making mistakes"
Start.
He got hit.
Nice.
Oh Jong-hyuk is out.
Very good, Lee Ju-yong. Well done.
"But the rhythm is interrupted
by Lee Jin-bong again"
Behind you.
"Serious"
Okay.
Sorry.
We're leading. Take your time.
We got it.
Good.
-We got it.
-Okay.
Nice!
Nice, Choi Seong-hyeon!
-He's strong.
-Nice, Choi Seong-hyeon.
-The bound.
-The bound. Gil-yeon.
Nice, Choi Seong-hyeon!
The bound. Gil-yeon.
"Park Gil-yeon is in danger
from the bounced ball"
The bound.
-The bound.
-The bound. Gil-yeon.
The bound.
Park Gil-yeon is good.
"Life shortened by ten years"
"Team Red 6, Team Blue 4"
It's okay.
One of us has to catch the ball.
"Even luck
does not favour Team Crisis"
-One of us has to catch the ball.
-Out.
What's this?
Watch out for the line.
It went over.
"Keeps dropping the ball"
It went over the line.
Get ready to catch the ball.
Go!
"A strategy
that doesn't go as planned"
-That's right.
-Gosh.
Jin-bong, catch it.
"It's hard for Team Crisis
to get into the rhythm"
Focus!
Behind you.
"Frustrated"
But Team Crisis is playing fiercely.
-Side pass.
-Nice...
"Hwang Chung-won"
Harder.
Nice.
"Hwang Chung-won successfully dodges
twice in a row"
Harder.
Nice, Hwang Chung-won!
Hwang Chung-won dodged well.
-Let's go!
-That's it!
That's it!
"Crazy moves,
dodges three times in a row"
Hwang Chung-won!
Hwang Chung-won
has been playing in the outfield.
Turns out he can play well
in the infield too.
-He's doing well.
-Yes.
-He's doing well in the infield.
-It's slippery.
-Catch.
"Hwang Chung-won dodges again"
Ready.
"He changes his target"
What a shame.
"Lee Ju-yong
from Team Crisis is out"
What a shame, Lee Ju-yong.
Ours.
Take your time.
"Team Red stays calm and steady"
-Come on. Give us a sign.
-Come on.
-Okay.
-Give signals.
-Very good. He caught it.
-That's right.
Oh Sang-young!
Come on.
Come on!
Yoon Jong-jin!
-Come on!
-Nice.
Oh Sang-young!
Nice!
"Oh Sang-young, Lee Ju-yong"
Go!
-This is ours!
-Go!
-That's right!
-Good.
-This is ours!
-Go!
-That's right!
-Good.
That's right!
-Good. Focus.
It's three to five.
Focus...
Good.
We're leading.
-Let's do a cheer.
-Go!
Focus.
"Kim Sang-wook"
Hit it. Here we go.
"Kim Sang-wook is out"
It's okay...
We're going to win.
Okay...
"Lee Min-gon"
-Nice.
-Okay.
Get hit.
Okay.
That's right!
Okay...
"Park Do-hyeon
from Team Survivor is out"
Watch your step on the line.
-Watch your step on the line.
-Park Do-hyeon is out.
He could have just gone next.
-No, again.
-Throw it straight.
Two, three.
-He got hit.
-That's it.
That's it.
"Park Gil-yeon is out"
-Keep defending.
-Right away.
Focus.
"Three to two, Team Survivor
continues to attack"
Hit it!
Okay, nice.
"At that moment, the ball
falls behind Jeong Hae-chul"
"Jeong Hae-chul, Lee Ju-yong"
Go!
Right away.
Go.
-Good.
-Okay.
"Jeong Hae-chul is out,
Team Red's chance continues"
-Right away...
-It's coming.
Get them all out.
"Last member of Team Survivor,
Gu Seong-hwi"
It's just Gu Seong-hwi now.
"Gu Seong-hwi
calmly dodges a crisis"
"Kang Jun seizes an opportunity"
It's just Gu Seong-hwi now.
"What is Gu Seong-hwi's fate?"
"Gu Seong-hwi is out,
Team Crisis wins"
Nice!
Good job.
"Too bad"
-We won!
-Okay!
That was good.
"Team Crisis wins with
their extraordinary fighting spirit"
I told you we could win.
We won.
We did really well.
It's life or death...
"The end of round three
of the Ten-person Elimination"
Good job...
"The torrential rain
doesn't seem to be stopping"
Round three is over.
"Six out of ten members
of Team Crisis will be eliminated"
Of the ten members of Team Crisis,
I'll announce the six survivors.
For the four people
who aren't called out,
sadly, it's time to say goodbye.
All right, six players.
"The third round
of the Ten-person Elimination"
"Who are the final six survivors?"
We'll announce it now.
It can't be helped.
It's a survival game
where one advances and one falls.
I have to win.
I sincerely hope I don't get
eliminated no matter what.
I'm confident.
Elimination? It hasn't hit me yet.
The first survivor.
The first survivor is...
"Who is the first survivor?"
Who will it be?
Hwang Chung-won.
Hwang Chung-won survives.
"Bitter"
Okay, the second out of nine.
The second survivor is
Lee Dong-gyu.
Lee Dong-gyu survives.
HID's Lee Dong-gyu, please move.
Okay, there are
eight members remaining.
The survivor among the eight.
"Who is the third survivor?"
Park Gil-yeon...
"The third survivor, Park Gil-yeon"
Park Gil-yeon survives.
Yes.
"The rest are getting impatient"
"Joy"
"Sorrow"
It's time for the fourth survivor.
The fourth survivor.
There's no turning back now.
Let's go all the way.
The fourth survivor is
Lee Ju-yong.
-Lee Ju-yong.
-It's Lee Ju-yong.
Lee Ju-yong survives.
Lee Ju-yong has really shown
his perseverance.
Lee Ju-yong. Yes, he's amazing.
Okay, there are
six members remaining.
Who will be chosen among the six?
The survivor.
This is the end.
I'll be eliminated after this.
How far can I go?
I don't think
I'm the team's black sheep.
Will they name me as the survivor?
The fifth survivor.
The fifth survivor is
Lee Jin-bong...
Lee Jin-bong survives.
"A dramatic last survivor
announcement for Lee Jin-bong"
The five of them
have been working hard.
But only one out of them
will survive
and say goodbye to the other four.
The last one out of the five.
This is the last player.
The sixth survivor.
Oh Sang-young...
Oh Sang-young survives in the end.
Out of the ten,
Yoon Jong-jin, Kang Jun,
Kim Sang-wook, and Lee Min-gon
are confirmed to be eliminated.
It's such a shame.
I worked so hard to get here.
There's no turning back for me.
I'm going to train hard
so that I can win in the end.
I worked so hard to get here.
I have to win.
I'm going to keep on surviving
until the end.
Today's Ten-person Elimination
started with 26 people,
and 16 people survived.
A total
of ten people are eliminated.
"Mixed emotions"
Round three
of the Ten-person Elimination
has come to an end.
Good job.
"The final round
of the Ten-person Elimination ends"
-Good job...
-What a shame.
"Survivors of Team Crisis"
"Hwang Chung-won,
Lee Dong-gyu, Park Gil-yeon"
"Lee Ju-yong,
Lee Jin-bong, Oh Sang-young"
"Back at the dormitory
after the Ten-person Elimination"
"The 16 players return
to their respective rooms"
It's so empty.
I should've done this.
"It was lively until yesterday"
"The space is clearly empty now"
Four out of seven people
in this room were eliminated.
Is there bad energy in the room?
"Is there bad energy in the room?"
More than half of them left.
When we were on "Steel Troops",
we were only with the members.
We were separated
from the other teams.
So we didn't have time to get close.
We were all strangers.
Now, it's a survival game
between acquaintances.
It feels so strange.
"It feels so strange"
I couldn't feel happy
even when I heard that I survived.
Because we sent them away so coldly.
It's a shame. Everyone did so well.
Someone has to be eliminated.
This is really a dodgeball battle...
This is really a dodgeball battle.
"The next morning"
"The players start their morning
by running topless"
It's time to play fiercely.
Since I've made it this far,
I have to get in no matter what.
I have to get a spot
in the national team no matter what.
I have to stay focused.
I worked so hard to get here,
I have to pass.
"While the players are training"
"The coaches are thinking
about how to pair up the players"
We'll choose two new captains
and divide them equally.
That's right. Eight to eight.
We've chosen a new captain.
Through the ace vote?
"The ace vote
was held the night before"
"Each player nominated two aces"
"Choi Seong-hyeon is an ace"
"Kim Jeong-woo,
a late starter but a hard worker"
"A rising new generation of aces"
"Voting for the aces is over"
Choi Seong-hyeon and Park Jun-woo
are now the new captains.
"Six votes for Park Jung-woo,
ten votes for Choi Seong-hyun"
Seong-hwi here.
Seong-hwi isn't bad either.
Jeong-woo isn't bad either.
Then Bo-geun.
"Park Gil-yeon"
If you divide it like this,
it's balanced, including strength.
Divide them into teams
that are equally matched.
"Later"
Two players from the losing team
will be eliminated
from the final selection.
Let's show them what we're made of.
I'll make it to the national team
no matter what.
Nice!
"The more you watch,
the more intense it gets"
Good!
"It's hard to predict
what will happen next"
Nice.
Defend!
Keep concentrating.
"What is the result
of the final selection?"
"After selecting the teams"
"The 16 players enter the arena"
"Entrance complete"
"Eight members of Team Blue"
"Eight members of Team Red"
It's a fierce battle to become
the national dodgeball team.
Iron Ball, Dodgeball Battle.
Before the final selection begins,
there will be a pre-match
with a benefit at stake.
The benefit
of the pre-match mission is...
"What is it?"
The right to choose one person
to be outed.
-Out? Just like that?
-Out?
The right to choose one person
to be outed is
when the match starts,
you can designate one more player
besides the regular outfielder
to be the first one out
from the infield.
To the outfield.
We can send one player
to the outfield first.
My goodness.
That's cruel.
The pre-match with the benefit
to designate an outfielder.
It's the Winning Throw.
"Winning Throw?"
What's Winning Throw?
Winning Throw?
"Turning heads"
The Winning Throw.
One person from each team
takes turns to attack and defend.
The team that scores more wins.
"Winning Throw"
Since it's a preemptive strike,
why don't we send
Kim Geon or Jeong-woo?
Okay...
-How about Kim Geon?
-Okay.
Okay, let's send Kim Geon.
I'll give it a try.
"Good idea"
What could go wrong?
-You can do it.
-With your speed, you can do it.
It's a one-on-one match,
so it's nerve-wracking
to be in the front.
Think about the direction
before you throw.
"Reliable"
The experienced
Jeong Hae-chul will go first.
"Number one shooter,
the experienced Jeong Hae-chul"
It will be good for those
with height advantage
to throw the ball fast.
"Agility, Park Gil-yeon,
Height, Lee Dong-gyu"
"Speed, Park Do-hyeon"
Let's be bold
and keep our usual passing speed.
Power isn't important.
We just need
to score with precision.
Let's give it a try.
"We can do it"
Let's begin the Winning Throw.
Team Park Jun-woo will attack first.
"Nervous"
The first players, please come out.
"The first team strikes"
Go!
"First shooter,
Jeong Hae-chul from Team Blue"
-Go!
-Good.
We'll win.
-Jeong Hae-chul!
-Okay.
Go!
"First shooter,
Kim Geon from Team Red"
Kim Geon!
Jeong Hae-chul will attack first,
and Kim Geon will attack second.
"The first shooter to take the lead"
The goalpost
is narrower than I thought.
The goalkeeper looks narrower.
You can do it!
"Nervous"
Don't be nervous. Just be precise.
Come on, don't be nervous.
Just do what you always do.
The order is important
in the Winning Throw.
I'll play with the determination
not to make any mistakes.
Since I'm the first player
for Team Red,
I have to be precise
and pre-empt the first move.
Don't be nervous.
Just do what you always do.
Throw it.
There's a lot of space to throw.
"Jeong Hae-chul shoots"
Okay...
"Goal"
"A clean shot into the net"
-Okay.
-Nice.
"Team Blue is off to a good start"
Great job.
Jeong Hae-chul.
It's okay.
It's okay. We just need to score.
Good.
-It's okay.
-It's okay as long as we score.
"Player change"
Kim Geon, use 70 per cent
of your strength.
That's fast enough.
"Oh Jong-hyuk encourages him
and boosts his confidence"
He has a head start.
Good.
"Glares"
Kim Geon, don't be afraid.
Don't look him in the eye.
"Defence, offence"
Ready.
"Team Red's momentum relies
on Kim Geon's hand"
"Start"
"Kim Geon's downward shoot"
"What will be the result?"
"Failed to score"
"Blocked"
"Jeong Hae-chul's cool defence"
"Team Blue succeeds
in making the head start"
-Jeong Hae-chul!
-Go!
He's indeed an ace.
It's good he went first.
It's okay...
-Kim Geon, it's okay.
-It's okay...
You did well...
-It's because you went first.
-That's right.
-Good job. It's okay.
-You didn't get hurt.
"Team Blue 1, Team Red 0"
Second players, come on out.
"Second players enter"
"Second shooter,
Kim Jeong-woo from Team Red"
Lee Dong-gyu from Team Blue"
Let's go!
Lee Dong-gyu versus Kim Jeong-woo.
Jeong-woo plays water polo,
so he must be good.
He's a water polo player.
But Dong-gyu might put pressure
on Jeong-woo.
Because he's big.
He's strong. Look at his arms.
"Lee Dong-gyu, the master
of extraordinary fastballs"
Ready.
I just think it's fun.
I always win when I'm having fun.
Let's play calmly.
I'm confident in myself.
"The designated outfielder
depends on this"
"Winning Throw"
Ready.
"How will the second player do?"
"Nervous"
"Lee Dong-gyu's power shot"
"Kim Jeong-woo's successful defence"
"Kim Jeong-woo accurately saw
the direction of the shot"
"Lee Dong-gyu's attack failed"
"Thrilled"
It's okay.
-Dong-gyu, it's okay...
Jeong-woo is so cool.
So cool.
The opposing team
has turned the tables.
Gosh, his arm...
Gosh, it's packed.
Spider Hands, Lee Dong-gyu.
Ready.
"Ready"
"The one who's going to score"
"The one who's going to block"
Gosh.
Nice!
"Precisely defended
with his long arm"
"Lee Dong-gyu guards the lead
by one point"
Did you see his reflexes?
"Team Blue 1, Team Red 0"
Jeong-woo, good job.
If you get to do it again...
"Team Red is eyeing
the next opportunity"
Kim Jeong-woo guards the lead
by showing good defence.
Lee Dong-gyu also relied on defence
to beat his opponent.
The third players, please come out.
-Go, Kim Seung-min!
-Go!
"Third shooter,
Gu Seong-hwi from Team Blue"
Gu Seong-hwi attacks first
and Kim Seung-min will defend.
-Ready.
-We're leading, so don't worry.
"Must stop the ball no matter what"
"Must score no matter what"
"Kim Seung-min successfully defends"
"Team Blue 1, Team Red 0"
If Kim Seung-min scores,
they'll have a chance
to even the score.
Control is more important
than speed.
Ready.
"He shoots"
It's okay.
"Kim Seung-min's shot
slightly missed the goal"
Okay.
The result of this round
is that both teams failed to score.
Park Jun-woo's team
is leading one to zero.
"Fourth shooter,
Park Do-hyeon from Team Blue"
-Let's go!
-Let's go, Park Do-hyeon!
"Disgruntled"
"Who is Park Do-hyeon's opponent?"
It's the ace.
Go, Ace!
"Fourth shooter,
Choi Seong-hyeon from Team Red"
Let's go, Choi Sexy!
They're both the most agile players.
Show us the power of speed.
How did they meet like this?
"Choi Seong-hyeon
versus Park Do-hyeon"
Let's even the score.
Take him out.
"I will kill you"
"Smiling"
"Suddenly serious"
"Goal"
"Park Do-hyeon shoots the ball
straight to the net"
"Team Blue scores another goal"
Block it. Just block it.
"Replay"
"His finger touched the ball"
"But unfortunately,
he failed to defend"
Now, Choi Seong-hyeon attacks
and Park Do-hyeon defends.
Choi Seong-hyeon is in a situation
where he must score.
I'm the captain and the ace.
I have to show them
what we're made of.
"Did he miss?"
"Choi Seong-hyeon failed to score"
That's it.
"The ball grazed the goal"
"What a shame"
With this score,
Park Jun-woo's team
leads two to zero
over Choi Seong-hyeon's team.
-Let's go!
"Fifth shooter
Park Gil-yeon from Team Blue"
"Fifth shooter,
Hwang Chung-won from Team Red"
"Power versus evil"
Park Gil-yeon
from Park Jun-woo's team
and Hwang Chung-won
from Choi Seong-hyeon's team.
The goal looks narrower.
It's filled up.
"Can they break the wall,
Hwang Chung-won?"
Ready.
"Park Gil-yeon shoots"
This one is going in.
"Goal"
"Bitter"
"Replay"
"Eye feint"
"Park Gil-yeon's patent"
"Successful goal"
It's okay...
We just need Chung-won
to score, right?
Yes, we just need him to score.
Chung-won, make the ball explode.
"Laughs"
If the remaining three score,
and all of them block,
it will be a tie.
"All three remaining shooters
must block to tie the game"
I have to score.
No matter who the opponent is,
I must challenge myself.
"Powerful shooter
Hwang Chung-won's attack"
"Goal? Miss?"
"Goal"
"Hwang Chung-won
makes Team Red's first score"
Good.
Good job...
"Replay"
"Attacks the corner precisely"
If Bo-geun scores, the game is over.
I'll end this game.
We just need to block their shots.
Isn't it two to one?
-Is it three to one?
-Three to one.
-Two points.
-The sixth players from both teams,
please come out.
Let's go!
"Sixth shooter,
Oh Jong-hyuk from Team Red"
Song Bo-geun from Team Blue"
-Okay, Song Bo-geun.
-Go!
Don't worry.
It's three to one for us.
"Team Blue has
a huge three-to-one lead"
Please.
He must get this ball.
He must block this ball.
"Team Red wants to snipe
even if it's just one point"
I have to stop it before it goes in.
Block at least one.
Don't make a mistake.
Then I can win.
"Goal"
"Team Red is in a crisis"
"Mixed emotions"
We just need to score a goal.
Song Bo-geun scores a goal.
It's four to one.
Go, Oh Jong-hyuk!
"If they fail this attack,
Team Red will lose"
"Please..."
"Goal"
"Oh Jong-hyuk succeeds
in his attack"
"As expected of Oh Jong-hyuk"
I knew it.
I didn't know
he could score like that.
"Winning Throw"
"Team Blue 4, Team Red 2"
We can win just
by blocking the ball.
If this goes in, it's over.
We have to block this one.
The seventh players,
please come on out.
All right...
Go...
Shall we do a chant?
Let's do it after we win.
"Team Red Lee Jin-bong is defending"
Park Jun-woo will attack first
and Lee Jin-bong will defend.
The match begins now.
Let's decide the result.
"Please, defend"
We have a good chance of winning.
Park Jun-woo's right shoulder
is not good.
"Park Jun-woo injured
his right shoulder during training"
Then Park Jun-woo...
Are you going to prepare
with your left arm?
Yes, I think my left arm
is better now.
"Shoulder injury variable"
Choi Seong-hyeon's team is losing,
but if they win this round,
Choi Seong-hyeon's team
has the chance to turn the tables.
"A chance to turn the game around"
"Nervous"
Ready.
"The fate of both teams
depends on one ball"
"Did Park Jun-woo score?"
"Please"
"The ball went outside the goal"
"We survived"
"It was close"
Still, he did well.
Good job, Jun-woo.
We can win if we block him.
It's okay.
"Because of Park Jun-woo's mistake"
"Team Red gets another chance"
Actually, I'm under
a lot of pressure.
If I don't score,
the eighth shooter Oh Sang-young
will have no chance.
Ready.
"Bong-ki's fire shot"
"Goal"
"Team Red succeeds in attacking
and catches up by one point"
Lee Jin-bong scores with a feint.
Good job...
"But Team Red is still ahead
by one point"
Good job, everyone.
This is a very critical moment.
Lastly, let's welcome
the eighth players.
"The last rush"
"The last shooter,
Oh Sang-young from Team Red"
Oh Sang-young.
"The last shooter,
Oh Ju-yong from Team Blue"
We meet again.
Gosh.
"The fate of both teams
depends on this final round"
Lee Ju-yong versus Oh Sang-young.
Sang-young is under
a lot of pressure right now.
"200 per cent pressure"
-Go!
-Go, Lee Ju-yong!
"Lee Ju-yong has a chance
to end the match"
-Go.
-Relax...
Sang-young, let's go.
-Let's redeem ourselves.
-Go, Lee Ju-yong.
"If Oh Sang-young succeeds
in scoring and intercepting"
"The match will be back
to square one"
"I'm going to end the match
with this attack"
Ready.
"Lee Ju-yong shoots"
"What will be the result?"
It's okay...
"Oh Sang-young successfully defends"
"Nice, Oh Sang-young"
It's okay.
-Just block him.
-Just block him. Good job.
It's okay, Ju-yong...
We'll win as long as we block him.
It will be amazing
if we get extra time.
Sang-young would go crazy.
If we score this goal,
our team will have a chance
to make a comeback.
We have to score no matter what.
Our team's victory flag
is in my hands.
We have to block this goal
no matter what.
Sang-young, forget about the team.
Save the game for yourself.
Please be quiet.
My heart hurts so much.
I feel like I'm going to faint.
Okay, Lee Ju-yong can do it.
Ready.
"Oh Sang-young
must score no matter what"
"Lee Ju-yong can win
if he just blocks him"
"A match that causes sweaty palms"
"What is the result?"
He blocked it!
We won!
We won.
"Team Red fails to get the benefit"
It's okay.
I lost.
You already did well.
You're amazing.
Even if we give them the benefit,
we still have a chance to win.
"Winning Throw"
"Team Blue gets the benefit"
"The night is getting darker"
"Goseong Stadium
in Gangwon Province"
"The players are waiting to enter
after the lights are turned on"
The captain's position
is always heavy.
Since I'm the captain,
I have to lead them and make sure
no one gets eliminated.
I'll make it to the national team
no matter what.
I can't lose
now that I've come this far.
I'm really going to do my best.
Dodge me.
I'll get a ticket
to the national team no matter what.
The Korean national flag
is on the line.
I'm going to win no matter what.
"The players enter"
It's a fierce battle to become
the national dodgeball team.
Iron Ball, Dodgeball Battle.
We will now begin
the final selection match.
The final selection match
will be two out of three rounds.
The first team
to win two rounds wins.
The losing team
will lose two players.
In order for our team
to avoid elimination,
it's important
to win the first round.
We have to win this time
no matter what.
Your goal is on the screen.
"Our goal?"
"The goal is to be
on the national team"
"The large Korean flag
is on the screen"
I'm feeling the pressure
and burden again.
"Nervous"
My blood is boiling.
Through the final selection match,
14 members will be selected
for the national dodgeball team.
I hope you'll do your best
to become the national team.
"It has finally begun"
"The final selection match
for the national team"
"Team Blue's captain, Park Jun-woo"
"Team Red's captain,
Choi Seong-hyeon"
Before the final selection match,
Park Jun-woo's team
received the benefit
to select one player
to be on the outfield.
Please select the player
who will be on the outfield
from the other team.
Captain Choi Seong-hyeon.
"One outfielder"
"Captain Choi Seong-hyeon
from Team Red is chosen"
Don't we have to pick one opponent
to go to the outfield?
But if we want to send away someone
who can't play well,
we're more than capable
of doing that.
He's the only one we can kick out.
-It's him, right?
-We think alike.
Choi Sexy.
-He's really good at dodging.
-Choi Sexy.
I believe in our team's skills.
So I will attack more
from the outside.
Choi Seong-hyeon is the outfielder.
We'll begin the match
with two outside players.
I'm going to trust my teammates
and do my best.
Let's survive no matter what
and keep going.
I'm going to crush you all.
We're going to win.
"Eight versus eight"
"What is the result
of the final selection match?"
We will now begin the first round.
We can do it.
Let's go!
-Go! Fight!
-Fire!
"Team Red outfielders,
Choi Seong-hyeon, Lee Jin-bong"
-Top!
-Team!
"Let's go, Team Blue!"
"Team Blue outfielder, Lee Dong-gyu"
"The decisive moment is approaching"
Okay, please come out
for the jump ball.
"Team Red's Kim Seung-min"
"Team Blue's Lee Ju-yong"
Let's go!
Let's do this.
Let's go. Relax.
"The players are determined"
Let's do this.
Let's go!
"So..."
"Which team will go first?"
The final selection match
will begin now.
Let's go all out.
I'm going to go all out.
Nice.
It wasn't easy to get here.
I have to win.
Focus on the game.
Our team has to win
to move forward together.
"I create the opportunity"
That's right. We can dodge it.
"For my team to achieve victory"
The players that will be
the national representative of Korea
is...
Introducing the 14 players
of Korea's national dodgeball team,
the Iron National Team.
"The 14-member Iron National Team"
The first opponent
for the warm-up match
is the high school
dodgeball team from...
That high school?
I don't think they're
that threatening.
I think we can wipe them out.
It's the girls' team.
The first warm-up match
for the national team begins.